const e="english",o=200,s=75,t=[{id:622,question:"",option:{a:"classroom",b:"programme",c:"July",d:"brother"},section:"<b>LEXIS, STRUCTURE AND ORAL FORMS</b>  <b>In questions 26 to 27, identify the word that has a different stress pattern from the others.</n>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:26,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:623,question:"",option:{a:"temperamental",b:"administrative",c:"circulation",d:"consideration"},section:"<b>LEXIS, STRUCTURE AND ORAL FORMS</b>  <b>In questions 26 to 27, identify the word that has a different stress pattern from the others.</n>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:27,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:624,question:"",option:{a:"toil",b:"rejoice",c:"enjoy",d:"log"},section:"<b>In each of questions 28 to 31, choose the word that does not have the same vowel sound as the others.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:28,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:625,question:"",option:{a:"key",b:"wind",c:"even",d:"people"},section:"<b>In each of questions 28 to 31, choose the word that does not have the same vowel sound as the others.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:29,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:626,question:"",option:{a:"granite",b:"die",c:"rice",d:"fight"},section:"<b>In each of questions 28 to 31, choose the word that does not have the same vowel sound as the others.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:30,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:627,question:"",option:{a:"bale",b:"saint",c:"plait",d:"gate"},section:"<b>In each of questions 28 to 31, choose the word that does not have the same vowel sound as the others.</b>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:31,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:628,question:"I do not think any sane person would have acted in such a ....... manner?",option:{a:" rational",b:"composed",c:"secret",d:"cruel"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:32,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:629,question:"Neither Agbo nor his parents ...... the meetings now?",option:{a:"attended",b:"attend",c:" has attended",d:"attends"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:33,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:630,question:"Modern dancing has become rather scientific and so requires .......?",option:{a:"bizzarre costuming",b:" some choreographic skill",c:"immmense instrumentation",d:"a rapping voice"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:34,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:631,question:"Had he considered his public image carefully, he ..... for his in the election? ",option:{a:"might have stooos aside",b:"would have stepped stood",c:" should have stepped down",d:"would have stood down"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:35,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:632,question:`The government which .....recruiting ....... workers suddenly stopped doing so?
`,option:{a:"are / its",b:"was / its",c:" is / their",d:"were / their"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:36,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:633,question:"Of course we all saw the culprit ....... and hit the man on the head?",option:{a:"approached",b:"approching",c:"approach",d:"approches"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:37,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:634,question:"A child that shows mature characteristics at an early age may be described as .......?",option:{a:"preconceived",b:"premature",c:"ingenuous",d:"precocious"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:38,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:635,question:"The company Director showed the contractor a ....... of the proposed office complex?",option:{a:"prototype",b:"photograph",c:"microfilm",d:"photocopy"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:39,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:636,question:"....... You come early to the new house, clean up my flat?",option:{a:"While",b:"By chance",c:"Should",d:"Should in case"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:40,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:637,question:"This imposing edifice, ....... a fortune to build?",option:{a:" had costed",b:"have cost",c:"costed",d:"cost"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:41,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:638,question:`They let him go in ....... to his age?

`,option:{a:"respect",b:"regard",c:"disregard",d:"consideration"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:42,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:639,question:"Some scientists are trying to ...... human beings in their laboratories?",option:{a:"imitate",b:"replicate",c:"implicate",d:"fabricate"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:43,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:640,question:"He does not seem to know how to solve the problem ...... ?",option:{a:"does not he",b:"does he not",c:" does he",d:"doesn't he"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:44,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:641,question:"These villagers ....... to grow rice?",option:{a:"used",b:"are used",c:"were used",d:"use"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:45,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:642,question:"Ade tried to ...... all memory of his dead father?",option:{a:"recall",b:"obstruct",c:"obiterate",d:"eulogize"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:46,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:643,question:"The weather is probably ..... appealing for people who live in Jos ..... for foreigners?",option:{a:"as / much as",b:"more / as",c:"less / than",d:"at least as / but"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:47,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:644,question:"The meeting was called to ...... divergent views on the subject of a national conference?",option:{a:"reconcile",b:"recommend",c:"re-present",d:"reconstitute"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:48,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:645,question:"The police came early enough to...... the bomb planted by the rioters.",option:{a:"diffuse",b:"insulate",c:"detonate",d:"defuse"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:49,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:646,question:"..... told of his impending arrival, I worked hard to make his short stay very comfortable?",option:{a:"Have being",b:"Have been",c:"Have I been",d:"Having been"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:50,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:647,question:"More ...... to your elbow as you as you campaign for press freedom?",option:{a:"power",b:"effort",c:"grease",d:"energy"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:51,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:648,question:"When Ajike met her ..... husband at the party, she felt like reconciling with him?",option:{a:"estranged",b:"strange",c:"carring",d:"loving"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:52,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:649,question:"They had to ...... the generator when the electricity failed?",option:{a:"light up",b:"fall back on",c:"switch on",d:"resort to"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:53,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:650,question:"The editor was not happy that the Nigerian press was hemmed ....... ?",option:{a:"up",b:"over",c:"across",d:"in"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:54,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:651,question:"Three quarter of the hostel ........ been painted and three quarter of the students ...... moved in.",option:{a:"has/ has",b:"has /have",c:"hace / has",d:"have / have"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:`Have is the root verb and is generally used alongside the pronoun I / You / We / Ye and They and plural noun. Generally, have is a present tense word. Has is used alongside the PRONOUNS He / She / It and Who and SINGULAR NOUNS.

Hence the sentence would read;
Three quarter of the hostel has  been painted and three quarter of the students have  moved in.`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:55,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:652,question:"A wide range of options ....... made available to the political parties during the recently concluded elections?",option:{a:"are",b:"were",c:"was",d:"is"},section:"<b>In each of the questions 32 to 56, fill the each gap with the most appropriate option from the list option from the list provided.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:56,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:653,question:"",option:{a:"resist",b:"salon",c:"confirm",d:"intact"},section:"  <b>In questions 57 to 58, identify the word that has the stress on the first syllable.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:`stress is the degree of force applied when pronouncung the syllable(s) of a word. the stress syllable is the syllable on which the speaker uses more muscular energy and breath effort when pronouncing a word. we have various degrees of stress patterns such as, primary stress, secondary stress, tertiary stress and weakly stressed.

bisyllabic (two syllable) words are usually stressed on the first syllable except the first syllable is a prefix.  example (DOCtor) is stressed on the first syllable but ''disprove'' is stressed on the second syllable because the first is a prefix, so it becomes (disPROVE). in the above question, all the options but ''saloon'' have a prefix. that means saloon has its stress on the first syllable.

Note however that, there are certain exceptions to the above rule when the word is either a ''Ã§ompound noun'' or a ''compound verb''`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:57,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:654,question:"",option:{a:"competent",b:"misread",c:"resign",d:"compel"},section:"  <b>In questions 57 to 58, identify the word that has the stress on the first syllable.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:58,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:655,question:"<u>Ch</u>urch?",option:{a:"feature",b:"chauffeur",c:"ocean",d:"machine"},section:"<b>In each of questions 59 to 62 choose from the option the word that has the same consonant sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:59,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:656,question:"Pas<u>t</u>?",option:{a:"wrestle",b:"preached",c:"castle",d:"pasture"},section:"<b>In each of questions 59 to 62 choose from the option the word that has the same consonant sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:60,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:657,question:"<u>Th</u>ank?",option:{a:"though",b:"thought",c:"thames",d:"thomas"},section:"<b>In each of questions 59 to 62 choose from the option the word that has the same consonant sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:61,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:658,question:"<u>S</u>ure?",option:{a:"cheer",b:"cheap",c:"charlatan",d:"church"},section:"<b>In each of questions 59 to 62 choose from the option the word that has the same consonant sound as the represented by the letter(s) underlined.</b>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:62,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:659,question:"The lecture seemed <u>interminable</u>?",option:{a:"unending",b:"boring",c:"interesting",d:"brief"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:63,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:660,question:"Had I known about their plan much earlier I would have <u>nipped it in the bud</u>?",option:{a:" stopped it",b:"intiated it",c:"squashed it",d:"promoted it"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:64,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:661,question:"What a <u>harmless</u> thought he has?",option:{a:"pericious",b:"pertinent",c:"pleasant",d:"perfect"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:65,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:662,question:`The town was all <u>agog</u> at his unexpected return?
`,option:{a:" on fire",b:"excited",c:"unexcited",d:"surprised"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:66,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:663,question:"The journalist's write-up contained a <u>plethora</u> of detail?",option:{a:"shortage",b:"simplicity",c:"complexity",d:"spectrum"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:67,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:664,question:"In his <u>naivety</u> he believed all the stories his friend told him?",option:{a:"artlessness",b:"stupidity",c:"friendliness",d:"incredulity"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:68,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:665,question:"Amina's performance in the examination <u>surpassed</u> my expectations?",option:{a:"was disappointing",b:"lacked merit",c:"was extraordinarily good",d:"amazed everyone"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:69,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:666,question:"As these boys never act in public, the police are now worried about their <u>convert</u> activities?",option:{a:"ignoble",b:"evil",c:"open",d:"cryptic"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:70,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:667,question:`The teacher taught the  <u>rudiments</u> of Chemistry to the 
first grade.`,option:{a:"elements",b:"fundamentals",c:"basics",d:"stupidity"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:71,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:668,question:"It isinconceivable that the rat devoured the cat?",option:{a:"contestable",b:"incomprehensible",c:"credible",d:"unimaginable"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:72,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:669,question:"In the latter part of his life, the famous soldier showed signs of <u>youthfulness</u>?",option:{a:"energy",b:"senility",c:"bravery",d:"vitality"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:73,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:670,question:"Some equatorial areas have a <u>sultry</u> climate?",option:{a:"a hot",b:" an inclement",c:"a temperate",d:" a stable"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:74,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:671,question:`There is much <u>apathy</u> towards reading among students nowadays?
`,option:{a:"enthusiasm",b:"indecision",c:"disinclination",d:"indifference"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:75,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:672,question:"Updating the Board's brochure is an <u>arduous</u> task?",option:{a:" an easy",b:"an annual",c:"am regular",d:"a difficult"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:76,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:673,question:"All wondered why the principal was <u>ambivalent</u> about the students' future?",option:{a:"anxious",b:"inconsiderate",c:"ambitious",d:"decisive"},section:`<b>In each of questions 63 to 77,choose the option opposite in meaning to the underlined word(s).</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:77,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:674,question:"YOUR sister should come with us tomorrow?",option:{a:"Should your brother come with us tomorrow?",b:"Should our brother come with us tomorrow?",c:"Should Ado's sister come with us tomorrow?",d:"Should my sister come with us tomorrow?"},section:"<b>In each of questions 78 to 80, the word in capital letters has an emphatic stress. Choose the option that best fits the expression in the sentence.</b>",image:"",answer:"c",solution:`In answering questions on emphatic stress, the statement which contradicts the emphasized word is usually the correct option.

From the question above, the emphatic stress is placed on 'YOUR', and the option which contradicts it, is option 'C'.

Should ADO's sister come with us tomorrow? No!

YOUR sister should come with us tomorrow?`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:78,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:675,question:"My neighbour BRUISED his thigh while playing football?",option:{a:"Did your neighbour break his leg while playing tennis?",b:"Did your neighbour fracture his thigh while playing football?",c:"Was your neighbour involved in an accident ?",d:"Did your neighbour play football yesterday?"},section:"<b>In each of questions 78 to 80, the word in capital letters has an emphatic stress. Choose the option that best fits the expression in the sentence.</b>",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:79,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:676,question:"They FLEW to Abuja?",option:{a:" Did they go Abuja by road?",b:"Did they fly to jos?",c:" How will they get to Abuja?",d:"Where did they fly to?"},section:"<b>In each of questions 78 to 80, the word in capital letters has an emphatic stress. Choose the option that best fits the expression in the sentence.</b>",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:80,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:677,question:"Oche's chief idiosyncrasy is a passion for pounded yam?",option:{a:"Oche's chief hates pounded yam",b:"Oche pounded yam",c:" Oche has a penchant for pounded yam",d:" Oche's chief likes pounded yam"},section:`<b>In each of questions 81 to 85, select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:81,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:678,question:"You must not attend the end-of year party?",option:{a:"It is not necessary that you attend the party",b:" It is necessary that you attend the party",c:"You do not have to decided whether to attend the party or not",d:"You have to decided whether to attend the party or not"},section:`<b>In each of questions 81 to 85, select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"'You must not attend the end-of year party'' this statement means that, attending the party is not compulsory or a necessity. it is optional",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:82,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:679,question:"The man reasoned that there ought to be a limit to sycophancy?",option:{a:"there can be no favour beyond a reasonable point",b:" sycophants need not talk all the time",c:"people should know when not use flattery",d:" sycophants should know when to grant people's requests"},section:`<b>In each of questions 81 to 85, select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:83,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:680,question:`Adawo is an imp?
`,option:{a:"Adawo behaves queerly",b:"Adawo behaves decently",c:"Adawo behaves differently",d:"Adawo behaves badly"},section:`<b>In each of questions 81 to 85, select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:84,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:681,question:"The solution lies in choosing between various negative alternatives?",option:{a:"the solution can be found in one of negative options",b:"the solution lies in choosing between the positively and the negative and the negative",c:"the solutions are many",d:" the solution is a negative one"},section:`<b>In each of questions 81 to 85, select the option that best explains the information conveyed in the sentence.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:85,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:682,question:"I cannot understand why Ali should serve in that <u>moribund</u> administration?",option:{a:"oppressive",b:"prodigal",c:"crumbling",d:"purposeless"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:86,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:683,question:"The conference Centre caters for <u>transients</u> only?",option:{a:"temporary guest",b:"professional",c:"permanent guests",d:"novices"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:87,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:684,question:"The <u>coalescence</u> of the groups created additional problems?",option:{a:" proscription",b:"fighting",c:"disbandments",d:"union"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:88,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:685,question:"As the triumphant rebels were returning to their base they met with a <u>serious reverse</u>?",option:{a:"a defeat",b:"an enemy",c:"an army",d:"a victory"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:89,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:686,question:"The village girl wore <u>sumptuous</u> clothes?",option:{a:" faded looking",b:"cheap",c:"expensive",d:" loose-fitting"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:90,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:687,question:"Any chief executive of an organization would find <u>radical</u> changes blocked at every turn?",option:{a:" developments",b:"ideals",c:"suggestions",d:"innovations"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:91,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:688,question:`Ugo has often been described as <u>belligerent</u>?
`,option:{a:"attractive",b:"patient",c:"innocent",d:"combative"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:92,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:689,question:"The men were <u>tardy</u> in offering help?",option:{a:"brave",b:"generous",c:"slow",d:"quick"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:`tardy means ineffectual, slow-witted, slow to act. These adjectives mean not arriving, occurring, acting, or done at the scheduled, expected, or usual time: tardy in making a dental appointment; late for the plane; an overdue bus.

Synonyms: tardy, late, overdueSynonyms: tardy, late, overdue

Antonym: prompt`,examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:93,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:690,question:"Funmi is just being <u>facetious</u> about her marrying a soldier?",option:{a:"unserious",b:"crazy",c:"serious",d:"unfaithful"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:94,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:691,question:"The professor discussed a number of <u>abstruse</u> topics?",option:{a:"esoteric",b:"relevant",c:"irrelevant",d:"useful"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:95,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:692,question:"Bose was angry because her friend called her <u>pilferer</u>?",option:{a:"hypocrite",b:"thief",c:"criminal",d:"liar"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:96,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:693,question:"While the hooligans exchanged blows, we looked <u>complacently</u>?",option:{a:"dejectedly",b:"sorrowfully",c:"questioningly",d:"contentedly"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:97,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:694,question:"Tade became <u>timorous</u> when she was asked to give the valedictory speech?",option:{a:"excited",b:"nervous",c:"aggressive",d:"happy"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:98,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:695,question:"The player kept on <u>gamely</u> to the end of the match?",option:{a:"amateurishly",b:"skilfully",c:"courageously",d:"stubbornly"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:99,hasPassage:0,category:"others"},{id:696,question:"Art lies in cherishing the initiative and <u>creative power</u> of each person?",option:{a:"potential",b:"strenght",c:"gift",d:"mind"},section:`<b>In each of questions 86 to 100 choose from the options nearest in meaning to the word underlined.</b>
`,image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"utme",examyear:"2001",questionNub:100,hasPassage:0,category:"others"}],a={subject:e,status:200,total:75,data:t};export{t as data,a as default,o as status,e as subject,s as total};
